accidents occur without any warnings no
matter how careful we are
whether at home or outside they can
prove to be a financial
an emotional burden for the entire
family although having a life insurance
and health insurance cover
is a good practice a personal accident
policy
adds an extra cushion against financial
losses
arising out of an accident in an
unfortunate event
of permanent or partial disability due
to an accident
this policy provides lump sum benefits
to help you meet long-term expenses
moreover in an unfortunate event of loss
of life
due to an accident the policy pays out
the insured amount
to the family members or nominees
ensuring
that long-term life goals are not
compromised
quarter group accident protect a group
personal
accident policy has a worldwide coverage
keeping you secure around the world so
what are you waiting for get in touch
with our expert
today
you